# Afonso Pinto

Sintra, Lisboa +351 912 008 773 afonso.pinto2710@hotmail.com



### **Short introduction**

Working in the IT field since 2021, most of this time spent as a Full-Stack Developer.

In 2021 I enrolled in 2 internships, one as a Full-Stack PHP developer and another as a UX/UI Designer.

Since January 2022 until August 2023, I worked as a Full-Stack .NET developer at FEGIME Portugal, here I was responsible for the planning and development from scratch of a webapp in which multiple users still rely on every day. I was also responsible of maintaining the company database using both SQL and SAP.

### Education

## LEVEL IV TECHNICAL COURSE | 2021 | ESCOLA SECUNDÁRIA LEAL DA CÂMARA

· Management and programming of computer systems

# **Experience**

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER | FEGIME | JANUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2023

- · Planning and development from scratch of a .NET webapp in which multiple users rely on every day to access company data,
- Database management
  Technologies used: C#, .NET CORE, SQL, SAP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

### WEB DESIGNER | DIGITAL XPERIENCE | OCTOBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

· UX/UI designer

Technologies used: WordPress, CSS, Elementor

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER | WEB & GAMBLE | MAY 2021 - JULY 2021

 Planning and development of a billing/management webapp using PHP Technologies used: PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS